Guide to the Sala Udin Papers, 1980-2005 AIS.2006.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Sala Udin Papers
1980-2005
1995-2005
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Udin, Sala
AIS.2006.01
23.5 Linear Feet (25 boxes)
Sala Udin, an activist and community organizer at local and national levels, served on Pittsburgh City Council from 1995-2005, representing Council District 6, which includes the Hill District, downtown Pittsburgh, and portions of the North Side and Oakland. The bulk of the materials in this collection document his time on city council and include subjects such as African-American and minority history, employment, and culture; Pittsburgh's financial crisis; and police accountability.
Previous Citation
Sala Udin Papers, 1980-2005, AIS.2006.01, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Arrangement
The Sala Udin Papers are divided into 16 series:
Series I. Act 47 -- Municipalities Recovery Act / Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority (ICA)
Series II. August Wilson Center for African American Culture
Series III. Citizen's Police Review Board
Series IV. City, County, and State Files
Series V. Correspondence
Series VI. Freedom Corner
Series VII. Mason Tillman Associates, Ltd.
Series VIII. Neighborhood Files
Series IX. Newspaper Clippings
Series X. Pittsburgh Works
Series XI. Plan B
Series XII. Subject Files
Series XIII. Sala Udin Personal Files
Series XIV. Urban Redevelopment Authority
Series XV. Women and Minority Business Enterprises
Series XVI. Audio/Visual Media
Biography
Sala Udin, whose given name is Samuel Wesley Howze, was born on February 20, 1943 in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, to William and Mary Howze. Along with eleven siblings, he grew up in Pittsburgh's Hill District in public housing. He graduated from Port Richmond High School in New York in 1961 and soon after joined the Freedom Rider Movement in the South. In 1964, Udin registered voters for the Mississippi Freedom Summer Project and was active in the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, Head Start Programs, and the Southern Christian Leadership Conference.
Throughout the mid-1970s Udin worked in social service agencies including as founder and Executive Director at the House of Crossroads, a drug treatment facility and the Multicultural Resource Training Center. He became politically active as a member of the Democratic Party. In 1995 he was appointed to the Pittsburgh City Council following the death of Councilmen Christopher Smith. Udin would later be elected to serve Council District 6 in 1997. District 6 includes the following neighborhoods: Allegheny Center, Allegheny West, Bedford Dwellings, Bluff, California-Kirkbride, Central Northside, Chateau, Crawford-Roberts, Downtown, Manchester, Middle Hill, North Shore, Perry Hilltop, South Oakland, Strip District, Terrace Village, Upper Hill, West Oakland. He was appointed by Mayor Tom Murphy to the Competitive Pittsburgh Task Force, which was commissioned to review the debt of the city caused by the rising cost of city services and to examine market driven options as possible solutions. Additionally, Udin served on the boards of the Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh and the Urban Redevelopment Authority.
As a member of City Council, Udin sponsored a referendum to create a jobs program called "Pittsburgh Works," leading to a petition drive to take his proposal straight to city residents. He also served on many committees, such as the Plan B Oversight Committee, which helped provide jobs for women and minorities, and the Disparity Study and Implementation Commission, which helped minority groups obtain jobs for the demolition of Three Rivers Stadium and the construction of Heinz Field and PNC Park. In both the 2000 and 2004 Presidential elections, he served as an elector representing the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. He served on council until 2005 when he was succeeded by Tonya Payne. The same year he lost his 29-year-old son, Patrice Amilcar Howze, to street violence in the Hill District on October 9, 2005.
Udin has also been active in theater. He starred as Becker in the August Wilson play Jitney in October 1982 at the Allegheny Repertory Theatre, and again in May 2008, as Holloway in August Wilson's play Two Training Running. He also starred in Wilson's plays Ma Rainey, Fences, and The Piano Lesson. In 1965, along with August Wilson and Rob Penny, Udin co-founded the Centre Avenue Poets' Theatre Workshop in the Hill District, Pittsburgh and the Black Horizon Theater in 1968. He was also involved in the founding of the August Wilson Center for African American Culture.
Since leaving public office, Udin has been serving as the president and CEO of the Coro Center for Civic Leadership's Pittsburgh chapter.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Scope and Content Notes
The Sala Udin Papers include materials related to the Pittsburgh Councilman's life and career. Subjects include Pittsburgh's financial crisis of 2003-2004 and its recovery process through Act 47 (The Municipalities Financial Recovery Act of 1987); African American employment and culture in Pittsburgh including the August Wilson Center for African American Culture and the International Center for African Music; the establishment and activities of the Citizen's Police Review Board; City, county, and state departments and activities; the Freedom Corner Memorial and civil rights history; Pittsburgh neighborhood development and organizational initiatives; the Pittsburgh Works job creation program; Plan B's creation of new stadiums; city planning and development materials relating to the Urban Redevelopment Authority; Women, minorities, and other disadvantaged business enterprises; and a variety of topical and personal files between the years 1980-2005.
Crime -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Public safety -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Education -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Housing -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Politics and government; Urban renewal -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Minority business enterprises -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Women-owned business enterprises -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Police brutality -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Unemployment -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Correspondence; Clippings (Information artifacts); Audiocassettes; Videocassettes; Politicians -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; African American politicians -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; City council members -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; City planning -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Labor; Social action; Ethnic groups; Politics; African Americans -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Industries -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Udin, Sala; Pittsburgh (Pa.). City Council; Pennsylvania. Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority for Cities of the Second Class; Mason Tillman Associates; Pittsburgh (Pa.). Citizen's Police Review Board; August Wilson Center for African American Culture (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh
- Act 47 - Municipalities Recovery Act / Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority (ICA), 2001-2005; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  Act 47, or the Municipalities Financial Recovery Act, of 1987 empowers the Pennsylvania Department of Community and Economic Development to declare municipalities as financially distressed. Distressed municipalities are granted nonresident wage taxes and debt restructuring or adjustment in exchange for developing a recovery plan with an independent agency. The independent agency is able to make recommendations on the city's organizational structure, finances, and services.
  In August 2003 the City of Pittsburgh laid off 446 employees, closed recreation centers and public pools, and eliminated various services. By February 2004 the city had its credit rating repeatedly downgraded, a cash shortfall threatening pension payments and payroll, and an independent audit calling into question Pittsburgh's ability to continue. In response Mayor Tom Murphy filed for distressed status in accordance with Act 47. Sala Udin and other city council members decided that despite the proposed cuts to city services and tax increases the financial recovery plan was necessary and voted to approve it. Since March of 2004 the City of Pittsburgh has worked with the Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority (ICA) and the Public Financial Management (PFM) Group to find solutions for its financial problems.
  The Act 47 series includes correspondence and concerns from citizens, emergency response agencies, environmental services, unions, and other stakeholders directly impacted by Act 47; ICA memoranda, lawsuits, and reports; and recovery plans and proposed solutions. The folders are arranged alphabetically.
  - Act 47 - Consultative Evaluation and Recovery Plans reports, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Act 47 - Recovery Plan, June 11, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Act 47/ICA - AFL/CIO, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cable Bureau, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Udin, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Department of Finance, City of Pittsburgh - 2004 Operating Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Responders - Fire Fighters re: station closures, lawsuit, and Fire Fighters Local No. 1, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Responders - Fraternal Order of Police (FOP) Presentation to City Council on Act 47 Plan, June 22, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Responders - Responses to Act 47 from Fraternal Order of Police and Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership (PDP), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Services, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Expenditure Projection for 2005-2009, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority (ICA) - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ICA - lawsuit, May 2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ICA - Memoranda, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ICA Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Charting Pittsburgh's Course Through Act 47, November 2005; 1.
    - Second Quarter Report to the ICA, August 2005; 2.
    - Report and Recommendations, circa 2004; 3.
  - ICA Reports - Appendix of Documents Submitted and Resubmitted by the City of Pittsburgh to the Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority, April 28, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ICA Reports - ICA drafts and amendments, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - ICA Reports - Results of the City of Pittsburgh Compensation Plan Review for the ICA for Cities of the Second Class, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Joey King (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh Financial Leadership Committee (PFLC) solution, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Oversight Board materials, 2001, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Oversight Board articles, 2004; 1.
    - Ethics Code amendment, 2004; 2.
    - ICA vs. Act 47, 2004; 3.
    - Udin statement, 2004; 4.
    - Veto of Bill 468, 2001; 5.
    - Proposed Act 11, 2004; 6.
  - Pittsburgh Financial Management, Inc. (PFM Group)/ Eckert Seamans, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Transmittal letter from the Mayor, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- August Wilson Center for African American Culture, 1996-2005; II.
  The series on the August Wilson Center contains materials related to the creation of the present-day August Wilson Center for African-American Culture. First called the African-American Cultural Facility, it later became the African-American Cultural Center of Greater Pittsburgh in 2002 and hosted a variety of cultural events before its renaming in 2006. Councilman Sala Udin served on its Board of Directors beginning in 2002 and remains (2011) an ex-officio member.
  The series includes its initial bylaws, articles of incorporation, board and committee meeting minutes and reports, site plans and designs, business plans and studies, fundraising, newsletters, programs, and research subject files, including one on Charles "Teenie" Harris. Also includes materials regarding to the International Center for African Music.
  - AACF - Regional Site Inventory Assessment, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AACF - Requests for Qualification, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Architectural competition, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Boards and Committees - Board of Directors, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boards and Committees - Executive Committee minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
  - Boards and Committees - Executive Committee minutes, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - Boards and Committees - Search committees, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Boards and Committees - Steering Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Boards and Committees - Steering Committee - Museum data, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Brochures, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Budgets, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Business Plan, September 5, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Business Plan, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Bylaws and Incorporation Articles, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "Case Statement" regarding Udin's problem with "A Living Heritage of Communication" theme for AACC (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Charette Analysis and Summary - Key themes, issues, and conclusions, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Collaborative sessions, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Construction and redevelopment planning, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Nathan Davis' reports, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Feasibility study for the African American Cultural Facility (AACF), 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Feasibility/Development Analysis report, May 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Final Interim Report, vol. 1, December 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Final Technical Appendices, vol. 2, December 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Foundations, Fundraising, and Grants - Heinz Endowment, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Foundations, Fundraising, and Grants - Fundraising, 2001-2005 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Grants, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Functional Strategy Draft, January 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Heroes Awards, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Idea bank deposits, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - International Center for African Music (ICAM) - Grants, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - ICAM Reports - Various reports, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Summary of ICAM Research report, 1.
    - AACC Draft - Public Program Plan, October 2, 2002; 2.
    - Henry Highland Garnet, 1815-1882, essay, September 7, 2002; 3.
  - International Center for the Music of the African Diaspora (ICMAD), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ICMAD - Closing Report Project Description, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - License Agreement for Conference Center, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Multi-Cultural Arts Initiative (MCAI) domain specific councils, 1990-2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Member lists (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - News coverage, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Plans for progress, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Program guides, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Programming our Vision", May 8, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Subject Files - Buxton history research, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files - Short-listed teams, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files - Jazz, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files - Hampton Museum, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files - Homewood slave cabin, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files - Jack n' Jill (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files - Kuumba Trust, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files - Smithsonian Museum (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files - Teenie Harris (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files - Various loose files marked "research", 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Citizen's Police Review Board, 1992-2005; III.
  The Pittsburgh Citizens Police Review Board (CPRB) is an independent agency created by voter referendum to investigate citizen complaints about improper police conduct. Sala Udin initially introduced the legislation to form the Board. After getting stuck in a series of debates and court challenges lasting nearly two years, Udin took the idea directly to the public and the legislation passed by public referendum. The referendum and its rules are governed by Title Six, Article VI of the City Code. The CPRB was based on a variety of similar models around the country including the CPRB in Philadelphia, materials of which are included in this series. The Board is comprised of seven members appointed by the Mayor and the City Council. The CPRB is limited to complaints regarding the City of Pittsburgh Bureau of Police and its officers.
  The records in this series includes agendas and meeting files; agreements, ordinances, and resolutions between the CPRB, the City of Pittsburgh, and the Pittsburgh Bureau of Police; board member appointments and searches; citizens' complaints; correspondence; court document transcripts; reports on CPRB activities, police investigations and complaints; and research material related to establishing a police review board. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Citizens for Police Accountability training and general files, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Citizens Police Review Board (CPRB) meetings and agendas, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CPRB nomination and appointments, 1997-2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CPRB referendum, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Letters of support, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Court Documents - Civil suits, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Court Documents - Class Action Suits (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Court Documents - Transcripts of hearings, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Memoranda, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - National Association for Civilian Oversight of Law Enforcement (NACOLE), 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - National Association Civilian Oversight Law Enforcement mail list, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Philadelphia Police Advisory Board, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Philadelphia CPRB, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Press clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Reports, 1998-2005 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Allegations Filed 1998-2004 report, 2005; 1.
    - Activities Report for 1997-1999, 2000; 2.
    - Interim Status Reports (3 reports), October 2000; 3.
    - Rules and Operating Procedures, 1998; 4.
  - Reports - Investigative Report to the District Attorney of Allegheny County Regarding the Coroner's Inquest of 6/28/95 Concerning the Fatal Shooting of Mr. Jerry Jackson which Occurred on 4/6/95, by Special Investigator Richard A. Sprague, July 29, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Reports - Police complaints and incidence reports, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Reports - Working Agreement between the City of Pittsburgh and the Fraternal Order of Police, Fort Pitt Lodge No. 1 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Reports - Resolution and ordinance reports (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Tasers, mental health, and gun violence concerns, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Tasers, mental health, and gun violence concerns, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- City, County, and State Files, 1994-2005; IV.
  The series on City, County, and State Files includes materials related to the City of Pittsburgh, Allegheny County, and the State of Pennsylvania's cultural, political, and social activities during Sala Udin's tenure as city councilman. Subjects include authorities, agreements, assessments, charters, committees, correspondence, finances, minutes, municipal departments, reforms, reports, permits, and studies between 1994 and 2005. The series is broken into three subseries: Allegheny County, City of Pittsburgh, and Pennsylvania. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Allegheny County, 1.
    The Allegheny County subseries is comprised of materials related to Allegheny County, Pennsylvania. Subjects include: property assessment and the Home Rule Charter.
    - Apportionment Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Home Rule Charter, 1995-2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Home Rule Charter - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Home Rule Charter - Preparing Allegheny for 21st Century, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Property Revaluation Project, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Regional Asset District, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Special Court Judge's Association, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - City of Pittsburgh, 2.
    The City of Pittsburgh subseries is comprised of materials related to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Subjects include: city council, city departments and authorities, employment, finances, housing, and taxes.
    - Asphalt Plant, 1995-2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Building Inspection, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - City Council, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - City Council Invoices, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Commission on Human Rights, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Comprehensive Municipal Pension Trust Fund, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Contracting and Procurement, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Department of City Planning, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Department of Engineering and Construction, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Department of Finance, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Department of Law, 1998-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Department of Parks and Recreation, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Department of Personnel, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Department of Public Works, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Disparity and Employment Studies, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Disparity and Employment Studies - Minutes, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Disparity and Employment Studies - Proposal for Employment Study, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Emergency Operations, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Equal Opportunity Commission, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Finance and Budget, 1998-2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Financial advisors, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Fleet maintenance, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hillman-Roderick Committee, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Historic District Preservation, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Homestead Exemption Tax, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Housing Authority of Pittsburgh (HAP), 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - HAP, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Information systems (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Intergovernmental agreements, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Parking Authority, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh for the 21st Century, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Property assessment, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Rating Agency, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Reapportionment Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Revenue Projections 2000-2004 (Major Accounts) report, November 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Special event permits, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Tax reform, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Telecommunications, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Water and Sewer Authority, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Pennsylvania, 3.
    The Pennsylvania subseries is comprised of materials related to the state of Pennsylvania. The materials in this series are primarily concerned with legilsature.
    - League of Cities and Municipalities, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Legislative mailing list (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Senate Bills, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1995-2005; V.
  The Correspondence series includes correspondence to and from Councilman Sala Udin and individuals, organizations, and companies locally and nationally between 1995 and 2005. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - African American Institute (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - African American Ministers Leadership Council, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Allegheny County Council, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny County Coroner's Office, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Allegheny County District Attorney, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Amachi Pittsburgh, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 7)